

Akash Kantrikar

Software Engineer

Profile

To seek a competitive and challenging environment where I can serve your organization and an enjoyable career for myself. Also a responsible and efficient individual offering around 2+ years of experience in IT industry, working predominantly on Python, Django, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Azure and DevOps Services.

Employment History

Software Engineer at SLK Software, Bengaluru

Nov, 2019 - May, 2022

- Worked on Django-PostgreSQL full stack web application using microservice architecture.
- Experienced on Microsoft azure resources like App Services, Azure
 Database for PostgreSQL server, Automation Account, Storage account.

Senior System Engineer at Infosys Limited, Bengaluru

Jun, 2022 - Present

Projects

AutoSol Datamart & Translation Services(SLK Software)

Mar, 2020 - Jun, 2022

- Technologies & Tools Used: Python 3.7, Django 2, PostgreSQL 11, Microsoft Azure, Azure DevOps services, Oracle database, psycopg2, cx_oracle, pandas, Postman, pg-admin, PyCharm, Mural board, SQL Developer.
- Responsible for creating Django REST APIs, creating PL/pgSQL functions, updating web application, Maintaining psql database from session blockers, Achieving psql database backup from periodically in Linux server using Crontab, handling po files from web application, providing continuous localization service, Migrating IaaS postgreSQl database to PaaS service.

<u>akashkantrikar@gmail.com</u>

9900942125

Pengaluru, Karnataka, India

Education

Bachelor of Engineering at Bapuji Institute of Engineering and Technology, Davangere

Aug, 2015 - Jun, 2019

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Python

Django

PostgreSQL

SOL

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Languages

English

Kannada

Konkani

Hindi

Hobbies

Badminton and Web series.